Travis Umbel, Junior Web Developer

Madison, United States, 262-492-5905, Umbelth94@gmail.com

LINKS	<u>Github</u>		
PROFILE	I am an upbeat, highly motivated worker with a diverse background and skillset. Mostly self-taught web developer with 2 years of experience able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.		
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY			
Jul 2022 — Present	Packaging Specialist, Octopi Brewing		Waunakee, WI
	 Operate machines and troubleshoot issues to ensure maximum production efficiency on the line Maintain quality product standards by routinely monitoring equipment and products Changeover machines to various packaging types Create and maintain SOP documentation Train new employees on efficient use of equipment and practices 		
Jan 2020 — May 2022	Optics Technician, Pike Te	echnologies	Fitchburg, WI
	 Tested quality of IR Microscope objectives with a Zygo VFA (Asphere + Laser interface) Machine Inspected, cleaned, and packaged a variety of mirrors and lenses used in various FTIR (Fourier TransformInfrared) sampling machines Operated a vacuum coating machine to coat diamond lenses with Aluminum or Gold Adhesion Interpreted diagrams for assembly of various parts 		
Jul 2019 — Jan 2020	Wire Saw Technician, GE Healthcare		Milwaukee, WI
	 Precise operation of Wire Saw to dice scintillator material, producing sensors for Computed Tomography (CT) applications Observed & recorded in-process data, alerting Operations Engineering of process abnormalities Monitored equipment performance to support routine maintenance, ensuring process control 		
Aug 2017 — May 2019	Sales Associate, Menards		Burlington, WI
	 Leadership role in a store remodel effort, team lead for the demolition and re-construction of shelving, pallet-racking, and new displays, as well as being in charge of organizing and storing the needed parts Temporary department manager for a new store set-up in charge of training new employees and teaching them SOP's for various tasks Created estimates for various guest projects, ensuring cost transparency & customer satisfaction Daily down-stocking/up-stocking Responsible for condensing overstock pallets bi-weekly 		
EDUCATION			
Dec 2023 — May 2024	Certificate, UW Madison	Online Bootcamp	Madison, WI
	Currently enrolled in an online Full-Stack web development bootcamp that covers MERN stack development, Node.js, NoSQL, and Javascript with an emphasis on working collaboratively with others via Git, emphasizing Agile development strategies.		
SKILLS	Node.js	CSS	
	MySQL	HTML5	
	React	JavaScript	
	jQuery	Git	